sistawigs.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy

**Your Personal Information**

We collect your personal information when you provide it to us as you place your order and register for  **Sistawigs.com  **account. As a result those actions, you might provide us your name, address, phone number, email address, zip code and credit card information. We use your information for the purpose of responding to your requests, process your order, provide you with support, and update you on your order. We do not sell your personal information to other parties.

 **Cookies**

(a) Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to your computer's hard disk to enable saving of your Site preferences, and other record-keeping purposes. Cookies in and of themselves do not personally identify users, although they do identify a user's computer. We do not combine personal information you provide to us with information collected through cookies. Most web browsers can be set to refuse cookies, although this may cause certain features of our Site or Service to cease functioning properly. The "help" portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. Please note, however, that if do not cookies, you will not be able to take advantage of some of our attractive features.

(b) Web beacons assist in delivering cookies and help us determine whether a web page on this Site has been viewed and, if so, how many times. For example, any hair/wigs image on this Site, such as an ad banner, can function as a web beacon.

(c) Log Files. When you visit the Site, web servers collect information "traffic data" (such as, for example, time and date, the address of the website from which you entered the Site) about your visit, which is stored as anonymous, aggregate data. Collecting such data may entail the use of IP addresses or other numeric codes used to identify a computer. Sistawig uses "traffic data" to help diagnose problems with its server, analyze trends and administer the Site. Your IP address is not linked to personally identifiable information, but is used to gather broad demographic data and to monitor statistics to improve the Service. Sistawig may also use your IP address to help diagnose problems with its server. IP addresses are also used to provide an audit trail in the case of any attempted illegal or unauthorized use of the Site.

 **Security**

Our Site incorporates physical, electronic, and administrative procedures to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information, including Secure Sockets Layer ("SSL") for all financial transactions we process. We use SSL encryption to protect your personal information online. Information collected bySistawig is stored in secure operating environments that are not made generally available to the public. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, Sistawig cannot ensure the security of any information you provide, and you do so at your own risk. Once Sistawig receives your transmission, we will make reasonable efforts and comply with industry practices to ensure its security on its systems.

 **Questions or Suggestions**

If you have any questions or suggestions, please email to [info@s](http://hairsmize.com/contact-us.html)istawigs.com

 **Policy Changes**

 **Sistawigs.com**  reserves the right at our discretion to make changes to these policies without notice. Please check this page periodically for changes. Prices, specifications, and availability of products are subject to change without notice.
